AARONLILLA WWW.AARONLILLA.COM

VV VV .AARONLILLA.CO

8025 W. Russell #2037, Las Vegas, NV 89113

(702) 630-6976

AaronJLilla@gmail.com

Skills & Technologies

















Summary

Junior/Mid-Level self taught Full Stack web developer specializing in React & Node.js development. Well-versed in several web languages and technologies and am capable of beginning to end design & development from scratch. I am capable and willing to perform any role required, enjoy learning bleeding edge technologies, and have a passion for all areas of web design and development. Has background in managment and customer service.

Work Experience

Supercritical Co2 Extraction Chemist Evergreen Organix

05/2017 to Current Las Vegas, NV

- Responsible for start-to-finish supercritical extraction of organic matter into high quality concentrate
- Distill crude concentrate using short path distillation
- Responsible for production run design to min-max yields depending on product quality.
- Created SOP's (Standard Operating Procedures) for main laboratory
- Prepared and executed all extraction and distillation of organic products to maximum capacity

Inventory & Packaging Manager Evergreen Organix

02/2015 to 05/2017 Las Vegas, NV

- Responsible for tracking and maintaining a multi-million dollar inventory in a high paced environment
- Fulfilling and directed shipping of large orders
- Maintained software for tracking inventory as well as occasional back-end system maintenance
- Managed a team of 6 successfully and constantly improved efficiency of team
- Calculated top and bottom selling products to assist company in maximizing profits.

Freelance Web Design & Development

01/2012 to Current

- Graphic design, Logo Design, UI/UX Design, General Web development for various clients.
- HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, React/Redux, NodeJS, PHP, Jquery

Education

High School DiplomaPalo Verde High School

Class of 2010 las Vegas, NV

Languages, Frameworks & Skills

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript ES6, React.js, Redux, Node.js, jQuery, Express, Socket.io, Photoshop, Illustrator, Cinema4D, MS Office & always excited to learn more!